

ANGELIKA SPECTER

@AngelikaSpecter



angelikaspecter@gmail.com



www.angelikaspecter.com



FRONT-END WEB INTEGRATOR

PROFILE

I'm Front End Developer based in Kiev, Ukraine, and I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work. I just starting my proffesional way of Front End Developing, and I upgrade a skills necessary to build great websites, as well as 5 years of experience in website design, corporate identity and magazine development.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END WEB INTEGRATOR

Information Center «GARANT» (may 2021 - present)

Buying and keeping records of domains. Connecting and configuring domains to hosting. Connection of additional services and provision of minimal domain protection. Development / editing / creation and maintenance of pages or sites. Integration of various services or development of separate functionality (sending messages to mail / phone, determining the country by IP address, etc.). Web content management.

WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Self-Employed (mar 2017 - apr 2021)

Design Landing Pages, online stores, corporate sites, interactive prototyping

WEB DESIGNER

KievProekt (jul 2017 - mar 2018)

Branding, Website Design, SMM

PRO PHOTOGRAPHY

Self-employed (jun 2010 - sep 2019)

Photographing of music festivals, city events, sports competitions. Studio photography - boudoir and nude photography.

LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian (Native)
- Russian (Native)
- English (A2)

SKILLS



EDUCATION

IT STEP "FRONT-END DEVELOPER"

jan 2022 - jan 2023

HTML5. CSS3. Materialize. LESS. JS. OOP. DOM. BOM. Cookie. Canvas. JSON. Ajax. EC6+. MVC. jQuery. Animation. NodeJS. Webpack. Angular. React.

HTML ACADEMY INTERACTIVE

2016 - present

HTML5. CSS3. Flex. Grid. Effects. SVG. JS. BOM. DOM. PHP.

IT STEP

dec 2014 - apr 2016

Adobe Photoshop. Adobe Illustrator. Adobe InDesign. Digital Photography. Design theory. Corporate identity and branding. Advertising design. Typography. Prepress. HTML5. CSS3. Autodesk 3ds Max. Autodesk Maya.

ACADEMY OF ADVOCACY OF UKRAINE

jun 2007 - may 2012

Correspondence department of the Faculty of Law